<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Starmer on keiron.xyz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/starmer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Starmer on keiron.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <copyright>GNU Free Documentation License</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/starmer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Warning About Keir Starmer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/a-warning-about-keir-starmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/a-warning-about-keir-starmer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Labour leadership election is nearly over, and Keir Starmer is going to win. The polls are clear, the endorsements are stacking up, and the party establishment has coalesced around him. But I&amp;rsquo;m here to tell you why this is a disaster waiting to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Starmer represents everything that went wrong with New Labour, wrapped up in a slick package and sold as &amp;ldquo;electability.&amp;rdquo; He&amp;rsquo;s the continuity candidate for a politics that gave us austerity, that failed to challenge neoliberalism, that prioritized respectability over principles. He&amp;rsquo;ll drag us back to the centre-right positioning that made Labour indistinguishable from the Tories on the issues that matter most. Mark my words: within two years, he&amp;rsquo;ll have abandoned every progressive policy we fought for, alienated the membership that built this movement, and returned us to the triangulation and focus-group politics that left millions behind. The establishment wants Starmer precisely because they know he&amp;rsquo;ll kill Corbynism and restore their control. Don&amp;rsquo;t say I didn&amp;rsquo;t warn you when he inevitably disappoints everyone who believed he could be different.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
