<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on keiron.xyz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on keiron.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <copyright>GNU Free Documentation License</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the 2024 General Election outcome</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thoughts-on-the-2024-general-election-outcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thoughts-on-the-2024-general-election-outcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Despite Labour&amp;rsquo;s sweeping electoral success, a deeper analysis exposes flaws in the party&amp;rsquo;s approach of shunning its leftist roots. The Conservatives&amp;rsquo; crushing loss masks a potentially fragile foundation beneath Labour&amp;rsquo;s apparent dominance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pre-election polls indicated that nearly half of Labour voters were motivated primarily by a desire to oust the Tories, with minimal enthusiasm for Labour&amp;rsquo;s policies or leadership&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This lack of genuine support became evident in areas where credible left-wing alternatives emerged. The Green Party&amp;rsquo;s success in securing four seats, including a significant victory over a (dreadful) Labour shadow cabinet minister in Bristol Central, signals a shift in urban, diverse, and millennial-dominated constituencies. The Greens&amp;rsquo; strong second-place showings in numerous Labour-held seats across major cities suggest a growing progressive discontent that Labour can ill afford to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New beginnings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/new-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/new-beginnings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What a night. What an absolutely incredible, euphoric, vindication of everything we&amp;rsquo;ve been fighting for.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m writing this at 6am on Friday morning, still buzzing from the most extraordinary election night of my lifetime. The TV is still on in the background, showing talking heads trying to process what just happened. They&amp;rsquo;re struggling because none of them saw this coming. None of them understood what we were building out here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
