<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on keiron.xyz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on keiron.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <copyright>GNU Free Documentation License</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Polanski</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/polanski/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/polanski/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I joined the Green Party on the day of the 2024 General Election. After everything that&amp;rsquo;s happened with Labour - the betrayals, the triangulation, the complete abandonment of anything resembling economic and social justice - I thought maybe it was time to look elsewhere. The Greens, at least, seemed to offer something different: environmental urgency combined with social justice, a politics that recognised the climate crisis as the defining issue of our time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the 2024 General Election outcome</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thoughts-on-the-2024-general-election-outcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thoughts-on-the-2024-general-election-outcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Despite Labour&amp;rsquo;s sweeping electoral success, a deeper analysis exposes flaws in the party&amp;rsquo;s approach of shunning its leftist roots. The Conservatives&amp;rsquo; crushing loss masks a potentially fragile foundation beneath Labour&amp;rsquo;s apparent dominance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pre-election polls indicated that nearly half of Labour voters were motivated primarily by a desire to oust the Tories, with minimal enthusiasm for Labour&amp;rsquo;s policies or leadership&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This lack of genuine support became evident in areas where credible left-wing alternatives emerged. The Green Party&amp;rsquo;s success in securing four seats, including a significant victory over a (dreadful) Labour shadow cabinet minister in Bristol Central, signals a shift in urban, diverse, and millennial-dominated constituencies. The Greens&amp;rsquo; strong second-place showings in numerous Labour-held seats across major cities suggest a growing progressive discontent that Labour can ill afford to ignore.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Free Electronic Health Record Manifesto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-free-electronic-health-record-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-free-electronic-health-record-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A specter is haunting the National Health Service – the specter of inefficiency and fragmented healthcare data. All the powers of the health sector have entered into a holy alliance to exorcise this specter: health administrators and bureaucrats, technology vendors and proprietary software giants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A tumultuous epoch of information silos, proprietary systems, and bureaucratic red tape has dominated our healthcare landscape for far too long. The time has come to establish a new paradigm, a paradigm that champions transparency, collaboration, and interoperability. We present this manifesto as a call to arms – a call for the liberation of healthcare data for the common good of the NHS and the well-being of its patients.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuck you Python</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fuck-you-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fuck-you-python/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s lay it out bare: Python irks me to no end. Imagine being in a relationship that&amp;rsquo;s less Romeo and Juliet, more Bonnie and Clyde on a bad day. It&amp;rsquo;s the kind of setup where even your cat gives you that &amp;ldquo;I told you so&amp;rdquo; look every time you sit down to code. Your friends stage interventions, your mam subtly suggests &amp;ldquo;seeing other languages,&amp;rdquo; but there you are, hopelessly entangled in Python&amp;rsquo;s embrace, as if it whispered sweet nothings in the form of syntactic sugar directly into your heart. For reasons beyond my own comprehension, walking away feels as impossible as not eating the 6 doughnuts you got reduced from the local Co-Op in a single sitting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In praise of nano</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/in-praise-of-nano/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/in-praise-of-nano/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the sprawling universe of software development, where complexity and feature-overflow often drown the essence of creativity, there sits a modest throne reserved for a tool that champions the elegance of simplicity: Nano. This text editor, often overshadowed by its more elaborate counterparts, deserves a sonnet of its own.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nano, the humble steward of text, serves as the unsung hero in the realm of code and prose. Unlike its brethren, which boast an arsenal of features and customisations, Nano prides itself on its straightforward demeanour. It&amp;rsquo;s the quintessential example of software that adheres to the philosophy that less, indeed, is more. In a landscape dominated by applications that strive to be jack-of-all-trades, Nano remains content in its mastery of one: allowing users to edit text efficiently and without fuss.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But you don&#39;t feel like other people</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/but-you-dont-feel-like-other-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/but-you-dont-feel-like-other-people/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m writing this from my shed. Not metaphorically - literally a converted shed that I rent in Aberystwyth, where I&amp;rsquo;ve been largely alone since March. Eunice moved to the Valleys after finishing her masters in Leicester - to where my family are, to where I&amp;rsquo;m from - which made sense at the time but feels increasingly unbearable now. Video calls aren&amp;rsquo;t the same. Screens can&amp;rsquo;t replicate the simple presence of another person, the way they breathe, the small movements that let you know you&amp;rsquo;re not alone in the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Warning About Keir Starmer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/a-warning-about-keir-starmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/a-warning-about-keir-starmer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Labour leadership election is nearly over, and Keir Starmer is going to win. The polls are clear, the endorsements are stacking up, and the party establishment has coalesced around him. But I&amp;rsquo;m here to tell you why this is a disaster waiting to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Starmer represents everything that went wrong with New Labour, wrapped up in a slick package and sold as &amp;ldquo;electability.&amp;rdquo; He&amp;rsquo;s the continuity candidate for a politics that gave us austerity, that failed to challenge neoliberalism, that prioritised respectability over principles&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Look at his record: he spent years trying to overturn the Brexit referendum, showing complete contempt for working-class voters who backed Leave. As Director of Public Prosecutions, he oversaw the prosecution of students and protesters whilst letting bankers walk free&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. This is the man who&amp;rsquo;s supposed to represent radical change?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Light in the Longest Month</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/finding-light-in-the-longest-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/finding-light-in-the-longest-month/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a pretty dour person by nature. Always have been. My default setting is to expect the worst, prepare for disappointment, and find the cloud in every silver lining. January in Wales doesn&amp;rsquo;t help - grey skies, endless rain, and a landscape that looks like it&amp;rsquo;s given up on joy entirely. But this year, stuck in the depths of winter, I&amp;rsquo;ve been wondering whether this has to be who I am forever.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Day Before Everything Falls Apart</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-day-before-everything-falls-apart/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-day-before-everything-falls-apart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow is election day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve got thousands of Labour voters who need reminding to vote, and nobody left to remind them. Our get-out-the-vote operation - the thing that saved us in 2017 - has collapsed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our Brexit position is political suicide, and everyone knows it except the people making the decisions in Westminster. We&amp;rsquo;re trying to be all things to all people and ending up as nothing to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m getting it from both sides. Remainers are furious we&amp;rsquo;re not just backing Revoke like the Lib Dems. Leavers think we&amp;rsquo;re betraying democracy with our second referendum nonsense. And I can&amp;rsquo;t blame either of them because our position makes no sense.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New beginnings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/new-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/new-beginnings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What a night. What an absolutely incredible, euphoric, vindication of everything we&amp;rsquo;ve been fighting for.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m writing this at 6am on Friday morning, still buzzing from the most extraordinary election night of my lifetime. The TV is still on in the background, showing talking heads trying to process what just happened. They&amp;rsquo;re struggling because none of them saw this coming. None of them understood what we were building out here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
